question_data = [
   {"type":"boolean",
     "difficulty":"easy",
     "category":"General Knowledge",
     "question":"The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
     "correct_answer":"True",
     "incorrect_answers":["False"]},
    {"type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "category":"General Knowledge",
    "question":"Vietnam&#039;s national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
    "correct_answer":"False",
    "incorrect_answers":["True"]
    },
    {"type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "category":"General Knowledge",
    "question":"A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
    "correct_answer":"False",
    "incorrect_answers":["True"]
    },
    {"type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "category":"General Knowledge",
    "question":"French is an official language in Canada.",
    "correct_answer":"True",
    "incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {"type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "category":"General Knowledge",
    "question":"You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
    "correct_answer":"True",
    "incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {"type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "category":"General Knowledge",
    "question":"When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {"type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "category":"General Knowledge",
    "question":"On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.",
    "correct_answer":"True",
    "incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {"type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "category":"General Knowledge",
    "question":"Ping-Pong originated in England",
    "correct_answer":"True",
    "incorrect_answers":["False"]
    },
    {"type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "category":"General Knowledge",
    "question":"A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
    "correct_answer":"False",
    "incorrect_answers":["True"]
    },
    {"type":"boolean",
    "difficulty":"easy",
    "category":"General Knowledge",
    "question":"Romanian belongs to the Romance language family, shared with French, Spanish, Portuguese and Italian. ",
    "correct_answer":"True",
    "incorrect_answers":["False"]
    }
   ]
